Level 6?
<Level 6>
絶対能力？
That's correct, level 6...
<Level 6>
そう　絶対能力だ
You will become the dream of Academy City.
お前は学園都市の　夢になるのだよ
Oh dear grandfather, I am becoming the dream of this city?
お爺樣　私がこの町の夢に
That's right.
そう　その礎になあ
Yes, the very base of it.
Yellow Marble to Marble Leader.
イエローマーブルよりマーブルリーダー
Arrived at location.
延着しました　これより搬入を開始します
Beginning drop-off.
Brown Marble, how's it going over there?
ブラウンマーブル　そっちはどうだ
Has the blue car been following you?
青い車はついて来てるか
As planned.
予定通りです
No more playing dumb.
茶番の時間は終わりだ
How about we get to the finale?
そろそろフィナーレと行こうじゃないか
Wait up.
待ってろ　この私が必ず
I shall surely...
Wha—?
What has...
何が
Geez.
ったく　何が楽しいのか知らないけど
I don't understand what you find fun about stuff like that...
That's one meticulously planned prank.
変の困怠いたずらですわ
What are you doing?
何の真似だ
Why are you here?
なぜ君たちがこんな所に
What in the worl—
一体どういう
木山先生　この車は囮です
Kiyama-sensei, that car is a decoy!
子供たちは乗ってません
The children aren't in it.
What?
何だと！
Oh wait!
Saten-san, hurry!
佐天さん　早く
What are you people doing?
おい　君たち何を
So cramped... Uiharu you're heavy... Please get in!
狭っ　初春重っ
乗ってください
I'll navigate.
私がなるします
Hurry up!
急いで　子供たちを助けるんでしょう
You're going to save the children, right?
Onee-sama!
お姉様
Now then...
さーて　あんたたちの相手は
you will be facin—
Erm...
えっと
Well...
ここまでで結構ですわ
You can drop me off here.
Th-This strange ability...
こ　この如何わしい能力は
You can think of it as the "Arrival of the True Hero".
シンチ登場とでも　申しましょうか
This looks like a very good place for me to demonstrate "Aerohand" — my ability.
<Areo Hand>
ここは　私の能力空気使いの見せ所のようですわね
婚后さん
Kongou-san!
ここは　私たちが引き受けますの
We will take control of the situation here.
お姉様は木山春生にお力添えを
Onee-sama, you go support Kiyama Harumi.
黒子
Kuroko...
分かった
Understood.
ちゃんとついてこなかったら　承知しないからね
Just hurry up and catch up with me, all right?
You're asking that while knowing I am Shirai Kuroko, Onee-sama's partner?
私を　お姉様のパートナー白井黒子と知ってのお言葉ですの
H-Hey...
ちょっ　人の決め台詞を盗らないでくたさいの
Don't go stealing someone else's tag line!
先輩
Sempai!
Okay!
オッケー
さあ　行くわよ
Now, let's go!
響き合う願いが今覚醒めてく
脑海中回响着的愿望现已苏醒
譲れない未来のために
为了绝不可相让的未来
巡り逢う運命を超えたその先に
只因在超越命运的前方
この想い輝くから
这份思念正闪耀着光芒
ここじゃない未来に
在那并非归属的未来
想い託してみては
寄存着这份思念
強さの本当の意味を
继续寻找着那
搜し続けてた
强大的真正意义
ありのままの痛みを
将各种痛苦
受け入れるその意味を
全部承受的意义
明日へ走り続ける君に知った
是奔向明天的你告诉了我
巡りゆく景色が今流れてく
那眼前的景色现已过去
手繰り寄せた世界の先
那紧牵着双手的世界的前方
降り注ぐシグナルを躰で感じて
身体已感觉到其中所倾注的信号
解き放つ今全てを
此刻解放所有一切
Just truthin my heart
いつだって迷わないよ
无论何时都不应迷茫
消せない想いがあるから
因为有着无法磨灭的思念
解き明かす真実から瞳を逸らさずに
直视那已经揭开的真相
I'll reach the next stage to realize all.
確かな絆信じて
请相信这份羁绊
まさか　あなたとコンビを組むなんて　思っても見ませんでしたわ
I never expected to be fighting alongside you.
この際　どちらの能力が上か　決着をつけませんこと
Why don't we use this occasion to see which of our abilities is better?
さっきの部隊が出発した少し後
A little while after the units we saw before had departed,
民間凡そという輸送車が二台 MAR本部から出て行くのだ
anti-skill surveillance satellites spotted two transport
vehicles disguised as civilians departing from the MAR.
あれ　この記録は
Huh these records...?
<Antiskill>
警備員の監視衛星で目撃されていました
恐らく
We are afraid...
そちらが本物
Those are the real ones.
私がまんまとダミーを掴まされたというわけか
And I was tricked into chasing the fake.
急ぎましょう
Let's hurry.
そいつら　もう目的地に着いてるみたいなんです
They seem to have already arrived at the destination!
場所は
Where is it?
23学区にある　使われていない推進システム研究所
It's a decommissioned propulsion system laboratory in the 23rd Academy District!
Take the next left!
この先の分岐を左に
Oh?
ほう　いいね
Good going.
もっとも　そのくらいでなきゃ
But honestly, if you were any worse...
摑まって
Hold on!
ぶっ殺し甲斐がねえもんだ
It won't be any fun to just kill you!
固法先輩
Konori-sempai!
何　今の
What was that?
おらおら　命懸けで逃げねーと
Now you have to run for your lives,
ぺしゃんこになっちまうぞぉ
or you will be smashed!
この声
This voice.
あの女か
That woman, huh?
御坂さん
Misaka-san?
なっ　何してるんですか　一体
Wh-What are you doing?
もっとスピード出して
Step on it!
言われなくてもやってる
I have been!
ごめん　私　間違ってた
Sorry.
I was wrong.
立場が違えば　私も同じことをしていたさ
If I were in your position, I would have done the same thing.
失敗の埋め合わせは ここで済むから
I'll make up for my failures here!
電撃が弾かれる
The electric shocks are deflected?
そんなもん効くと思ってんのかあ
You thought that stuff would work?
Then...
だったら これで
This would!
響き合う願いが今覚醒めてく
hibikiau negai ga ima mezameteku
The resonating wishes awaken now
譲れない未来のために
yuzurenai mirai no tame ni
for a future we can not give up on.
I already expected that.
分かってんだよ
そんな
巡り逢う運命を超えたその先に
No way...
meguriau unmei wo koeta sono saki ni
Beyond the fate we encounter,
<Railgun>
てめえの超電磁砲の射程が
Including the fact that your railgun only has a 50 meter range.
50メートルしかねえっつうのも含めて
この想い輝くから
kono omoi kagayaku kara
this hope will shine.
＜Bank>
てめえの能力は丸と書庫に曝されてんだから
Your ability is well known because of The Bank!
ここじゃない未来に
koko ja nai mirai ni omoi takushite mite wa
Entrusting our hope on a future that we haven't seen,
想い託してみては
強さの本当の意味を
tsuyosa no hontou no imi wo sagashi tsuzuketeta
we seek the true meaning of strength.
なんてやつ
What a bitch!
次に分岐も左に
Take the next left, too!
搜し続けてた
通信？
Communication?
ありのままの痛みを
ari no mama no itami wo ukeireru sono imi wo
I understood the meaning of accepting pain as it is,
Heh I missed.
外したか　まあいい
Who cares.
受け入れるその意味を
グリーンマーブルそっち行ったぞ　潰せ
Green Marble, they went your way.
ashita e hashiri tsuzukeru kimi ni shitta
by observing you continuously run for tomorrow
明日へ走り続ける君に知った
Smash them.
<Antiskill>
こちらグリーンマーブル　現在警備員に…
This is Green Marble...
Huh?
currently, we hav—
巡りゆく景色が今流れてく
meguriyuku keshiki ga ima nagareteku
The seasons come and go.
こっから先は　一歩も通さないんだから
We won't let you go any further!
手繰り寄せた世界の先
taguriyoseta sekai no saki
Beyond the world we strive for,
That's right.
そうだ　こっから先のランプは何とかこっちで抑えじゃん
We have control of the ramp ahead of this spot.
降り注ぐシグナルを躰で感じて
furisosogu shigunaru wo karada de kanjite
I feel the signal that rains down without form.
悪いが上から圧力がかかって　うちらはこれが精一杯じゃん
Sorry but we are being pressured from above and can't do any more than this.
解き放つ今全てを
tokihanatsu ima subete wo
Release everything now
<Antiskill>
どうして警備員が
Why is Antiskill...
Just truth in my heart
いつだって迷わないよ
itsudatte mayowanai yo
I will never be lost.
いいから　とっとと子供たちの所に行くじゃん
Forget that and just get to the children quickly!
消せない想いがあるから
kesenai omoi ga aru kara
Since I have the hope that I will never lose.
解き明かす真実から瞳を逸らさずに
Damn.
tokiakasu shinjitsu kara me wo sorasazu ni
Do not look away from the truth we reveal.
役立たずのゴミ共が
Useless rubbish.
だったら自分でやってやろう
I will stop them myself.
I'll reach the next stage to realize all.
遠く感じてた　君が走る背中を
tooku kanjiteta kimi ga hashiru senaka wo
I felt like your back was far away as you continued running.
また
Again?
しっかり摑まってろ
Hang on tight.
itsukara darou konnanimo chikaku ni kanjiru
But when did I begin to feel you so near by?
いつからだろう
こんなにも近くに感じる
fuan kakushi kirezu ni semaru sora wo miageta
Unable to hide my worry, I looked up at the sky coming near.
不安隠し切れずに　迫る空を見上げた
So annoying.
冗長と
いい加減諦めろ
Give up already!
傷ついた記憶　いつか乗り越えるよ
kizutsuita kioku itsuka norikoeru yo
These traumatic memories I will one day overcome.
No matter much you resist, it's impossible to save the children!
てめえらがどんなに足搔こうか
ガキ共を助けることなんさ　できんとねえんだからよ
憧れは　能力を今　呼び起こす
akogare wa chikara wo ima yobiokosu
Admiration awakens my ability now,
Even still, I vowed to continue resisting!
それでも　足搔き続けると誓ったんだ
守りたいものがあるから
mamoritai mono ga aru kara
since there is something I want to protect.
巡りゆく　景色胸に　駆け上がるだけ
meguriyuku keshiki mune ni kakeagaru dake
As the scenery comes back to my mind,
私は
A teacher can't give up on a student!
痛みは風に消えてく
itami wa kaze ni kieteku
the pain dissapears into the wind.
教師が生徒を諦めるなんてできない
Believe in Judegelight
Believe in Judgelight
運命さえ　撃ち抜いて
unmei sae uchinuite yoake wo kono te de tsukurou
Shoot through even fate, make the dawn appear with these hands.
夜明けをこの手で造ろう
当たり前じゃない
Of course not!
変えていく勇気変わらない心で
kaete iku yuuki to kawaranai kokoro de
With courage to change and a heart that stays the same,
何が何でも　あんたを送り届ける
I will save you no matter what!
私は　そのためにここにいるんだから
That's why I'm here!
I believe myself and precious emotion.
I believe myself and precious emotion
打ち砕く　この想いで
uchikudaku kono omoi de
I smash through with my emotions.
What can you do now?
今更てめえに何ができる
とっとと死ねぇぇ
Just die!
Misaka-san?!
御坂さん
始まりの　光の中　誓い合う
hajimari no hikari no naka chikaiau
In the brand new light,
果てなき闇を裁くこと
hate naki yami wo sabaku koto
we vow to judge the endless darkness.
恐れてた　孤独の渦　溺れることに
osoreteta kodoku no uzu oboreru koto ni
I was afraid of drowning in the whirlpool of loneliness,
だけどもう振り向かない
dakedo mou furimukanai
but I won't turn back anymore.
Just truth in my heart
いつだって迷わないよ
itsudatte mayowanai yo
I will never be lost.
消せない想いがあるから
kesenai omoi ga aru kara
Since I have the hope that I can never lose.
それがどうした
What did that do?
I can predict all the attacks you do!
てめえの攻撃は　全部見知ってるんだからよ
解き明かす　真実から　瞳を逸らさずに
tokiakasu shinjitsu kara me wo sorasazu ni
Do not look away from the truth we reveal.
だったら　見せてやるわよ
Then...
I'll reach the next stage to realize all
I'll show you!
I'll reach the next stage to realize all.
黒子
確かな絆信じて
Kuroko!
tashika na kizuna shinjite
Believe in those irrefutable bonds.
お姉様
Onee-sama!
I can shoot things other than coins!
私が飛ばせんのは　コインだけじゃない
これが私の全力-だ
This is my full power!
なーに
What?!
<Teleport>
ったく　いきなり空間移動してちゃうんだから
Geez.
You suddenly teleport.
御坂さん　白井さん
Misaka-san, Shirai-san!
大丈夫ですか　怪我は
Are you all right?
You're not hurt?
平気　平気
Oh we're fine.
助かった 礼を
Allow me thank you for your help—
待って
Wait.
Huh?
それは　子供たちを助けてから聞かせて
I'll listen to that after we save the children.
A Certain Scientific Railgun
ああ
Yes.
- Academy City - 23rd District -
How is it?
どうだ　分かりそうか
Can you figure it out?
もうちょっと　プロペクトが堅くて
Just a little more.
The protection is hard.
Geez.
全く
お姉様が一人残らずお片づけになるから
Just because you clear every single one of them...
しょ　しょうがないじゃない
I had to do it.
さっきは中に誰もいないなんて思いもしなかったんだから
How could I have known over there that no one would be inside?
あった！
Found!
今この施設内で　一ヶ所だけ消費電力が桁違いな場所
There's one place in this facility that's using far more electricity than any other place.
最下層ブロックの
The blocks furthest down...
見つけた
Found it!
春上さん　春上さん
Haruue-san!
春上さん
春上さん　えっと　ここのシステムは
Haruue-san...
Umm...
What is the system like here?
ちょっと待ってて　向こうのほうを見てくる
Wait a second.
I'll look over there.
Please.
お願いします
待ってろ　今助けて
Wait for me.
I'll save you now...
おい　大丈夫か
H-Hey, are you all right?
This sound...
この音　まさか
No way...
この　くそガキ共が
You fucking bastards.
No way...
うそっ　あんた
You...
さっきの礼だ
Here's my thanks for what you did back then!
Shirai-san, Misaka-san!
白井さん　御坂さん
貴様
Why you!
今のは
That was...
I feel great!
ウイっすとしたぜ
舐めた真似してくれやがって
Making a fool out of me...
That bitch...
あいつ
キャパシティダウンですね
It's capacity down!
御坂さんが言ってた　能力者だけを苦しめる音だって
The sound that only hurts ability users Misaka-san was talking about!
この音が
This sound is...?
What the heck?
何だてめえ
それが分かったところでどうするってんだ
How is knowing that going to help you?
I remember the updated version is larger and the
speakers that have been mounted can't be moved.
確か　改良型は大きくて　固定したスピーカーを移動できないって
ああ　だがこの施設中に設置してある
Oh?
But they are placed all around this facility.
なんなら一個一個壊して回るか
You want to go around breaking them one by one?
それだけ大きなシステムなら
If it's that big of a system,
制御できる場所は限られます
there aren't many places where you can control it.
この建物の中を調べた限り
From what I see by analyzing the building...
それができるのは　私たちが先までいった
The only place where it could be done is where we had been until just now...
中央管制室
The central control room!
初春
Uiharu...
Then do it.
だったら　やってみろっつうの
やれるもんならなあー
If you can, that is.
ったく　ゴチャゴチャうるせえガキだ
Geez.
What a noisy bastard.
せっかくいいもん見せてやろうってのに
I was going to let you see something nice.
能力体結晶の完成っていうな
The completion of the Ability Body Crystal.
なんでよ
Why?
あんただって 犠牲者じゃない
You were a victim also.
お爺さんの実験体になって
Becoming a test subject for your grandfather...
能力を暴走させられて
Forced to have your ability go out of control...
なのに
Even still...
犠牲なんかじゃねえよ
I was not a victim.
権利を得たのさ
I was given the privilege.
私から生まれた　この種を花開かせて
Letting this seed be born — to sprout and to bloom...
That can't be...
それは　まさか　ファーストサンプル
The first sample.
<Level 6>
絶対能力を生み出す権利をなあ
The privilege to give birth to Level 6!
<Level 6>
絶対能力？
Level 6?
そうだ
That's right.
<Level 6>
こいつはこれから 学園都市初の絶対能力者になり
This will become the very first Level 6 in Academy City.
このガキ共の力を使ってなあ
By using the power of these children!
Huh?
まさか　春上さんを
No way...
You're using Haruue-san?!
<Level>
特定波長かにおける　強さを超えた受信能力
A receiver ability that surpasses her ability level under specific wavelengths...
こいつの能力は 能力体結晶と共振するのに　実に都合がいい
Her ability is very well suited to resonate with the Ability Body Crystal.
<Telepathy>
高位の精神感応は稀少だからな
Since high level Telepaths are rare, after all.
Why?
なぜだ
なぜまたこの子たちなんだ
Why is it them again?
なぜこの子たちばかり苦しめるんだ
Why must they always have to suffer?
なに
Oh come on.
ちょっとばかりこいつらの頭の中の現実ってやつを拝借するだけだ
I'm only renting out the Reality in their brains.
<Personal Reality>
自分だけの現実
Personal Reality...
呼び方なんかどうでもいい
I could care less what it's called.
要はその 脳内活動を司る神経伝達物質
It's just the neurotransmitters that control brain activity...
とりわけ　眠れる暴走能力者のそれを採取し
I will make sure that I collect it from the ability users who are also asleep.
ファーストサンプルと融合させる
I shall then merge it with the First Sample.
それによって能力体結晶は抑止力を獲得
By doing so, the Ability Body Crystal will obtain control capability.
完全なものとなるのさ
Thereby becoming complete.
あのじじはそのことに気づかず
However, that old bastard didn't notice and only seemed to care about making minor changes.
ひたすらこいつのマイナチェンジに気を取られてたようだがな
さてあとはこいつを
Now all I have to do is...
止めなさい
Stop that!
What?
そんなことをして
If you do that and these children wake up in an out of control state...
もしこの子たちが暴走状態のまま覚醒したら
<Poltergeist>
学園都市は空前の乱雑開放に見舞われ壊滅する
Academy City will experience an out-of-this-world Poltergeist activity and be devastated.
上等じゃねえか
That's perfectly fine.
神ならぬ身にして天上の意志に辿り着くもの
The one who reaches the will of
heaven without the body of a god...
そのための学園都市だろうか
That's what the Academy City is for!
<Level 6>　　　　
絶対能力さえ誕生すりゃ
When a Level 6 is born, a city like that will be needless!
こんな町　用済みだろうかよ
手　焼かせんなよ
Don't give me more work to do.
木山先…
Kiyama-sensei!
Just lie there obediently.
てめえはそこでおとなしくしてろ
Saten-san!
佐天さん
Which one?
どれ　どれなの
Which one is the Something-Down thing?
その何とかダウンってのは
てめえ面白いこと言ってたな
You were saying something interesting.
This voice...
この声
Skill Out aren't guinea pigs?
<Skill Out>　　　　
武装無能力集団はモルモットじゃねえ
そう武装無能力集団だけがモルモットじゃねえ
That's right.
Skill Out aren't the only guinea pigs!
お前ら全員がモルモットだ
All of you are guinea pigs!
学園都市は実験動物の飼育場
Academy City is a farm full of laboratory test animals!
All of you bastards are farm animals without exception!
てめえらガキは一人残らず家畜なんだよ
Misaka-san!
御坂さん
そろそろ止めといく
I'm putting an end to it no—
Huh?
何だ
What?
モルモットだろうか何だろうか
Whether or not we're guinea pigs,
そんなのは　知ったことじゃない
we don't care!
これって
Th-This is...
佐天さん
Saten-san!
ガキがもう一匹？
Some other bitch?
Why can you still move?
なんで動ける
私の友達に 手を出すなあ
Quit messing with my friends!
音が
The sound is gone!
放て 心に刻んだ夢を
hanate kokoro ni kizanda yume wo mirai sae okizari ni shite
Fire away! Leave behind the future and the dreams engraved in your heart
未来さえ置き去りにして
限界など知らない　意味無い
genkai nado shiranai imi nai
It knows no limits and has no meaning
この能力が光り散らす
kono chikara ga hikari chirasu sono saki ni haruka na omoi wo
My power will radiate these distant feelings
もういい　分かったよ
Fine now.
I understand.
その先に遥かな想いを
てめえらこの施設ごと 纏めて吹き飛ばしてやんよ
I'll blast you all along with this laboratory!
こいつはてめえの能力を解析して作ったもんだ
This was built through analysis of your ability.
歩いてきた　この道を
aruitekita kono michi wo furikaeru koto shika
If I could only look back on the path that I tried to walk
<Railgun>
てめえの超電磁砲より強力にな
It's made much stronger than your railgun.
振り返ることしか
ったく　モルモットだの　家畜だの
Geez.
出来ないなら
Calling us guinea pigs and farm animals...
dekinai nara ima koko de subete wo kowaseru
I would destroy it all here and now
どんだけ自分を憐れんだらそこまで逆怨みできんが
今ここで全てを壊せる
How little do you think of yourself to have so much hate for others?
暗闇に堕ちる街並み
kurayami ni ochiru machinami hito wa doko made tachimukaeru no?
The streets descend into darkness... How far will people go to resist?
<Electro Master><Level 5>
電撃使い　超能力者
Electromaster Level 5,
you are simply a piece of data in this city.
この町じゃてめえなんざただのデータ
人はどこまで立ち向かえるの
そうだ　減らず口をたたくデータだ
That's right.
加速するその痛みから
kasoku suru sono itami kara dareka wo kitto mamoreru yo
I'm sure I'll be able to protect someone from this increasing pain
Data that talks back.
学園都市はね　私たちが　私たちで居られる
Academy City is the best place to be —
it's where we can be ourselves.
誰かをきっと守れるよ
最高の居場所なんだ
Looking！The blitz loop this planet to search way.
Looking! The blitz loop this planet to search way.
私一人じゃできないことも
Things we can't do by ourselves,
Only my RAILGUN can shoot it.今すぐ
Only my RAILGUN can shoot it. imasugu
Only my RAILGUN can shoot it now
みんなと一緒なら遣り遂げられる
we can do together with everyone.
身体中を　光の速さで
karadajuu wo hikari no hayasa de kakemegutta tashika na yokan
A certain premonition that ran through my body at the speed of light
それが
That's...
You guys aren't humans.
てめえらは人間じゃねえ
駆け巡った　確かな予感
ただのサンプルだ
Only samples!
それが学園都市だ
That's what the Academy City is!
放て！心に刻んだ夢を
hanate! kokoro ni kizanda yume wo mirai sae okizari ni shite
Fire away! Leave behind the future and the dreams engraved in your heart
My...
私の　私だけの
Only my...
未来さえ置き去りにして
限界など知らない　意味無い
genkai nado shiranai imi nai kono chikara ga
It knows no limits and has no meaning
この能力が光り散らす
hikari chirasu sono saki ni haruka na omoi wo
My power will radiate these distant feelings...
その先に遥かな想いを
お疲れ様
Good work.
助かりましたわ
You were a great help.
これで
This is it?
Yes.
プログラムは完成だ
The program is complete.
あとは
Now only...
大丈夫なの
It's all right.
絆理ちゃんがねぇ
Banri-chan says she believes in you.
先生のこと　信じてるって
先生？
Sensei...?
どうして　目の下に熊があるの
Why do you have bags under your eyes?
いろいろと　忙しくてねぇ
I've been really busy lately.
本当だ　髪も伸びてる
Yeah, really.
Your hair has grown long, too.
でも　先生だ
But, it really is sensei.
木山先生だ
It really is Kiyama-sensei.
お前たち
You kids...
衿衣ちゃん
Erii-san,
私の声　聞いてくれて　ありがとう
thank you for hearing my voice.
Please allow me to say this...
今度こそ　言わせてくれ
ありがとう
Thank you.
Dear My Freind  Every day and night
dear my friend - every day and night
Always be with you
always be with you
Dear My Friend Every day and night
dear my friend - every day and night
何と申すのでしょう
Oh, how should one say it?
One man army? Violent as a lion?
孤軍奮闘？　獅子奮迅？
Always be with you
always be with you
Even after Shirai-san got afraid and ran off, I went up against countless enemies one after the other.
白井さんの打ち消すいて逃げ出した後も
私たった一人でなめる敵は
話しても　まだまだ足りないまま
hanashite mo madamada tarinai mama
Just talking with you isn't nearly enough
ちぎっては投げあ　ちぎっては投げあ　そーれ
Oh, so it was Kongou-san who stopped the rumored large scale Poltergeists?
<Poltergeist>
では　噂されていた大規模乱雑開放を食い止めたのは
夕焼けが　街を染めてゆく
yuuyake ga machi wo someteyuku
The city is dyed red by the sunset
婚后さんだったのですね
さすがですわぁ
That's just like you!
Not yet?
思うように　なかなかいかないって
まだかなぁ
omou you ni nakanaka ikanai tte
Things never turn out the way I want them to
もうすぐだよ
It's soon!
早く来ないかなぁ
I hope she gets here soon.
衿衣ちゃん　初春さんたちは
Erii-chan, where are Uiharu-san and the others?
気づいたら　一緒に泣いていた
kizuitara issho ni naiteita
Suddenly, I realized that we were crying together
すぐに追いつくから先に行っててって
They told me to go ahead; they said they'll catch up in a moment.
それにしても遅いなぁ
Even so, they're late.
This is a day of celebration.
せっかくの記念日なのに
恋も　夢も　花も　虹も　風も
koi mo yume mo hana mo niji mo kaze mo
Love, dreams, flowers, rainbows, and the wind
早くしないと間に合いませんよ
We need to hurry or we'll be late!
ぜんぶ掴もうよ
zenbu tsukamou yo
Let's take hold of them all
御坂さんと白井さんが遅刻なんて　珍しいですね
It's unusual for Misaka-san and Shirai-san to be late.
ダイジョウブ元気出して
daijoubu genki dashite
Don't worry, cheer up
全く　お姉様ったら　今日に限って寝坊なさるなんて
Geez.
Out of all the days to wake up late,
Onee-sama chose today to be the one...
私がそばにいるから
watashi ga soba ni iru kara
I'll be by your side
うっさい　あんただってぐっすり寝てたじゃない
Shut up.
You were sound asleep as well!
今日のミス　悔むより　今乗り越えて
kyou no misu kuyamu yori ima norikoete
Stop crying over spilled milk and make the most of what you have
でも意外でした
But it was unexpected that Misaka-san thought up an idea like this.
御坂さんがこんなアイディアを思いつくなんて
ダイジョウブ  迷わないで
daijoubu mayowanaide
Don't worry, don't lose your way
何言ってんの
What are you saying?
御坂さんらしい実にロマンチックなアイディアじゃない
It was a really romantic idea that Misaka-san thought up!
まだ見ぬ未来へと向かって
madaminu mirai e to mukatte
We're heading for an unknown future
Ah.
It's not like that!
そんなんじゃないわよ
ずっと　歩いてゆこう
zutto aruiteikou
Let's just keep walking forever
Oh, Shirai-san?
あ　白井さん
Dear My Freind  Every day and night
dear my friend - every day and night
えっ　まだ着いてないの
What? You still aren't here?
いや　用ってわけじゃないんだけどね
Oh no it's not some task or anything but...
Always be with you
always be with me
例の人　意識を取り戻したそうよ
That person we were talking about earlier seems to have regained conciousness.
Dear My Freind  Every day and night
dear my friend - every day and night
事情調子が始まったけど
The interrogation has begun but it's not going to be an easy task to get her to talk.
簡単に口を割りそうにないよね
Always be with you
always be with me
そうですの
I see.
私だって　いろいろ悩むけど
ええ　ありがとうございました
Yes.
watashi datte iroiro nayamu kedo
I worry about a lot of things too,
Thank you.
What?
何
It's going to take some time until we understand everything.
まだまだ　全容を解明には時間がかかりそうですわ
考えても　答えは出ないまま
kangaetemo kotae wa denai mama
but thinking about them won't lead to an answer.
Hmm?
こうしてはいられませんの
Oh, there's no time for this! We need to hurry!
急ぎませんと
Oh!
あ　あれ
That!
見上げれば　きらきら一番星
miagetara kirakira ichibanboshi
I look up and see the first glittering star of the night.
来た
They're here!
Here we go!
きれいだね　ふと笑顔こぼれた
kirei dane futo egao ga koboreta
How beautiful; I unexpectedly smiled.
愛も　傷も　過去も　今も　明日も
ai mo kizu mo kako mo ima mo asu mo
Love, scars, the past, the present and the future,
せーのー
すべて受け止めよう
subete uketomeyou
accept it all.
木山先生
Kiyama-sensei!
ダイジョウブ  勇気だすよ
daijoubu yuuki dasu yo
Don't worry. I'll have courage.
お誕生日 おめでとう
Happy Birthday!
私はひとりじゃないから
watashi wa hitori ja nai kara
Since I'm not alone.
Get well soon, Sensei!
諦めず　躊躇わず
akiramezu tamerawazu ippo fumidashite
Take the first step.
先生早く良くなってね
頑張るから
We'll work hard, too.
待ってるよ先生
We're waiting for you, Sensei!
一歩踏み出して
僕も
Me too!
ありがとう　木山先生
Thank you, Kiyama-sensei!
ダイジョウブ  迷わないで
daijoubu mayowanaide
Don't give up or hesitate.
大好きだよ
We love you so much!
まだ見ぬ未来へと向かって
madaminu mirai e to mukatte
We're heading for an unknown future
ずっと　歩いてゆこう
zutto aruiteikou
Let's keep walking forever
dear my friend - every day and night
Dear My Freind  Every day and night
Always be with you
always be with you
dear my friend - every day and night
诸神字幕组Bluray计划《某科学的超电磁炮》就此划上圆满的句号
感谢各位一如既往的支持 给予我们信心 帮助我们克服重重困难
always be with you
感谢staff们的辛勤劳动，宝宝，小la，小夜子，小苏
小狼，小展，娜夏，蘑菇猪，代班的空空和小疯，还有竭力而为
本当退屈しないわねぇ
It really never gets boring...
A Certain Scientific Railgun
Thanks to all the staff,
who stayed up late
or woke up earlier
to work on this anime.
- See you next season!
Presented by Ayako-Fansubs
The End
(for now)
この町は
Here in this city.
欢迎到www.kamigami.org继续关注《某科学的超电磁炮S》